Too slow.
Pervy Sage!
I'm not gonna let you!
I can see it.
Please, just give up already.
Pervy Sage!
I'm not gonna let you!
Stop, Naruto!
You're the one he's after!
But—!
If it keeps going like this—!
What's going on?
It's those guys—!
I'll tear off your seal
in one fell swoop!
You certainly know
how to waste my time.
Boruto!
Take Naruto and get away!
What?
There's no way I can do that!
We came here to protect Naruto!
Don't forget that!
I'm not going to let you!
Go!
But—!
Let go!
Let go of me!
I won't let you get away!
Let go!
The Power to See the Future
It doesn't seem like
he followed us.
I'm still wrapping you up!
Let go!
Please let me go!
Settle down.
Please!
Undo this!
And then what?
Go and save him!
What else?!
Are you sure you'd win
if you went back?
Now you've gone and done it!
I guess I'll go look for its owner.
Just who are you, anyway?
So heavy!
Cha!
Think carefully about
why he did all of that
to allow you to get away.
You saw Urashiki's moves too,
didn't you?
My eyes can see the future!
What he said…
I don't think it was just a bluff.
So, he really knows
about the future?
That's impossible.
Whoever he is,
I've never heard of a jutsu
that enables one to see the future.
Still, until we figure out
what his trick is…
That's why we can't abandon him!
Boruto…
I never abandon my friends!
Hey, you got that right!
I said, you can't go!
Let me go!
As long as we can't
figure out his jutsu,
there's no chance of winning.
Don't you understand that?
That blood!
Hey, wait!
Give us more details!
I don't know for sure yet,
but I want to test something out.
Anyway, just come with me!
A child, is it?
What's going on here?!
Who is that enemy?
You have to wake up now,
or we'll be in trouble!
Can you hear me?
I don't know who you are
or where you're from.
But you should stop doing
such dangerous things!
How about it?
Let's stop wasting
each other's time.
If you give that man to me,
I'll spare you your life at least.
He found us!
No, he couldn't have…not yet.
There's no need to die,
saving a man you know
nothing about, is there?
What am I doing?!
Why am I risking my life
for someone I don't know?
Despite all appearances,
I'm quite tolerant, you know.
I don't want to end up
hurting an innocent child.
I could find you quite easily
with my eyes,
but I don't want to waste
any strength unnecessarily.
Such a stubborn brat aren't you?!
We did it!
Damn it, what's going on?
Do you have eyes in the back
of your head or something?
How relentless.
Putting me through
all this trouble.
How can you easily
evade our attacks?
Can they do it?
Didn't I tell you already that
my eyes can see the future?
Fire Style: Dragon Flame Bomb!
So, you brazenly snuck back?
Your friendship is so touching.
Toad Oil Bomb!
An attack like that is futile.
Earth Style: Mud Wall!
They're quick to flee.
Did you see that?
Yeah, I did.
The blood that got on his clothes
dried quicker than mine.
Let's end this now, shall we?
It went just like
you said it would.
You're reckless, taking a big risk
just to verify that.
If our attack was too obvious,
he would've gotten suspicious.
Blood, eh?
I see!
I see?
Does that mean you've figured out
how his jutsu works?
The blood that got on his clothes
dried faster than yours.
In other words—!
In other words?
That's all, ya know!
That's exactly what I said!
Well then, did you figure it out?
I don't have a clue either.
Could it be possible that
Urashiki released heat
from within himself earlier?
No. I don't think there were
any signs of that.
Is there a chance that he used
something like a Wind Style?
Same.
What?! C'mon!
Explain it so that
I can understand too!
If we consider how blood can dry,
there are three ways.
He dried it with heat
he produced himself.
He was around a lot of wind, or…
A longer duration of time elapsed,
just for him.
A longer duration of time?
What do you mean?
The way he boasted about
being able to see the future
has been bothering me.
I thought he was just bluffing…
However, it could be half-true.
Half?
Instead of having a premonition
of the future…
What if he actually
goes to the future,
then uses some way
to come back to the present?
Come back?
No way!
Maybe he can turn back time.
So, he has another ability aside
from the Transportation Technique?
Without a doubt…
That would explain all the weird
phenomena up until now.
I found you!
You're not getting away anymore!
Be careful!
If he can turn back time,
it's gonna be bad!
So, you finally realized it?
Yes, time is on my side!
I'll smother your breaths
before you even realize it!
What a fidgety brat.
However, I've read all your moves.
Even if only a few seconds
pass for you…
For me, I can relive the moment,
several…no, dozens of times!
And it allows me to select
the best possible move!
Initially, this ability was
a defensive jutsu.
But against idiots like you,
I can easily use it offensively!
Why you—!
Yes, get angry!
That makes my job much easier.
I won't let you get away this time,
Naruto Uzumaki!
Ninja Art: Toad Mouth Trap!
We are inside the belly of
the Great Toad of Mt. Myoboku
I see…so I'm inside a stomach.
You do such interesting things!
Even if you can turn back time,
I've deduced that it's only
for a few seconds.
Otherwise, we'd have been
dead long ago.
So what?
In other words,
even you can't go back to
the moment before
you entered the belly!
Don't tell me you plan on
dissolving me in stomach acid?
How pitiful that you think you can
stop me with something like this!
Reserve your strength, you two.
Didn't I already tell you?!
I can replay the same moment
dozens of times…
…and select the best possible move!
All before you can even blink!
I'll begin by eliminating
the nuisances,
and proceed at my leisure.
This is…
Quite strange!
What's going on?!
We got you.
I told you we're inside the belly.
And the air in here is
filled with acidic poison.
Since it's colorless and odorless,
it's hard to detect.
Even if you can endure it for
a little while, after ten minutes,
the poison begins to
paralyze your entire body.
No way!
You've been reliving
that earlier attack
over and over again, haven't you?
That means,
the poison's effect on you
is many times stronger
than its effect on us.
In spite of being on a lower rung
of existence than a monkey…
…you're pretty arrogant,
aren't you?!
Let's do this!
Right!
That's what you get!
Did you see that just now?
Amazing, Big Bro Naruto!
My feet went out from under me!
We did it!
Yeah!
That jutsu earlier was amazing!
Yeah.
Should we call it…
Naruto Stream?
Huh?
I don't know why, but…
It has a nice
refreshing ring to it!
Right?
It's over, Urashiki!
It's over?
I wish you would stop
getting carried away
with underestimating me.
Do you wanna get beat up some more?
He's not bluffing.
He still has something
up his sleeve!
Next time on Boruto:
Naruto Next Generations:
"The Last Battle: Urashiki."
I'm gonna beat you all to death!
THE LAST BATTLE: URASHIKI